welcome to Counter-Strike 2 mapping Academy I'm Sami "Chimonahehe" Alayoubi
欢迎来到《反恐精英 2》地图学院 我是来自 Eagle One 开发团队的 Sami "Chimonahehe" Alayoubi,
from the Eagle One development team and I'm excited to go over how to make a map
很荣幸为您详细的介绍
for Counter-Strike 2 from start to finish
为《反恐精英 2》制作地图所需要的一切知识
the engine behind this game, Source 2, is an extremely powerful tool the purpose of this video is to teach
起源2是一个非常强大的工具
skills that are important to source2 workflow for those who are coming over
本视频的目的是向那些有起源1、虚幻、Unity 等其他引擎经验而转向起源2引擎
from Source1, Unreal, Unity and other engines it is also designed with those
的创作者们传授起源2地图开发的工作流程中一些重要技巧
who have Source2 experience and are looking to pick up some techniques and insight along the way
同时也可以为有起源2开发经验的创作者们提供一些新的技巧和知识
By the time we are finished with this tutorial you will
当我们共同完成本教程时,您将能够
have built from start to finish a Counter-Strike 2 map with a solid
从头到尾设计一张《反恐精英 2》地图,并充分地理解
understanding of the engine fundamentals and Source 2 workflow
起源2引擎的基本原理和工作流程
I have a passion for teaching and level design that has grown through the dozens
我有很强的热情来传授这些地图关卡设计知识
of published Source 2 maps and game modes made throughout the years seeing
我已经制作了许多张起源2的地图和游戏相关模式
how this engine is capable of making any type of game makes me excited that
这个引擎如何能够制作任何类型的游戏
Counter-Strike 2 is finally moving over and bringing its worldwide audience
让我感到兴奋的是反恐精英2最终将在全球范围内推出
I'm hoping that my experience mapping for this engine can inspire you to
我希望我在该引擎上绘制地图的经验能够激励您
create the Counter-Strike 2 map of your dreams so let's get started
创建梦想中的《反恐精英 2》地图,让我们开始吧
to access the Workshop Tools after downloading them for the first time just
（译者注：您现在需要在STEAM库中右键Counter-Strike 2 选择属性 点击DLC选项卡
find your Counter-Strike GO in the library and select Workshop Tools when
然后安装Workshop Tools,随后启动时选择Workshop Tools，视频中演示的是CS2内测时期的方法，已经过时)
prompted create a new addon gives us the ability to name our new project for
现在创建一个新的插件，并以这个视频系列的名字
now academy works just well for our series and since it's where all our work is
将我们的插件命名为academy，创建的工作就是这些
going to go let's set it as default and launch our tools
让我们将其设置为默认项目，然后启动我们的工坊工具
our academy addon has created a Content folder where it stores raw files such as
我们的academy插件在如视频所示路径下创建了内容文件夹,其中存储着我们项目的原始文件
this vmap and a game folder where a compiled file such as vpks will be stored
还有在game目录下也创建了一个文件夹,其中将存储编译后文件,例如vpk文件
oh and sorry if you don't have a ray tracing capable graphics card you
很遗憾，如果您没有支持光线追踪的显卡
can't compile your maps at all the GPU path tracing won't be shown in editor
那根本无法编译您的地图,编辑器里也无法显示光线追踪效果
as an option either you can still however fast compile and be limited to a non-vis
不过您仍然可以选择快速编译,但只能得到没有vis(决定地图各区域是否可视的程序)
non-light map preview that looks like Doom 3 lighting
以及没有光照的预览,看起来就像Doom3的光照效果一样
once the tools finish loading select Hammer under the tools button
一旦工具完成加载,选择工具按钮下的CS2 Hammer工具,
we're starting with a new map which gets stored as a .vmap file in your
我们将从一张新地图开始,该地图以 vmap 文件形式存储在您的
content directory on the left hand side are all the different tools that will be
内容文件夹中,左侧是用于创建地图的所有不同工具,
used to create the map these ones shown here may have more additions in future
如下所示这里可能会在未来的 Hammer 更新中添加更多内容。
Hammer updates the top left contains a different
左上角包含不同的
manipulation tools of the meshes objects navigation and entities that make up the
网格对象导航和构成
map we'll explain these editing and viewing selections later in the video
地图的实体的操作工具,我们将在视频后面解释这些
selecting the layout button gives a variety of different options to fulfill
选择布局按钮会给出各种不同的选项
your Source One Hammer gold Source Hammer plus plus or Worldcraft Nostalgia
满足还愿您在金源,起源1Hammer,Hammer++或其他工具软件中的布局
within each of these you can select all the different lighting views as well
在每个选项中您可以选择所有不同的光照预览,同时
pressing shift Z will focus on the camera view your mouse is currently
按 Shift Z 将聚焦于您的鼠标当前悬停的相机视图,
hovering over pressing it again will go back to the selected layout
再次按下它将进入返回到选定的布局,
to get the most accurate look at how the editor will reflect the final product be
以最准确地了解编辑器将如何反映最终产品,请
sure to find this tone mapping scale option by clicking the tiny arrow on the
务必通过单击
far right and selecting Auto and check enable pose processing
最右上侧的小箭头并选择“自动”并选中启用姿势处理来找到此色调映射比例选项,
understanding the theory behind level design that is based on brushes and
了解起源2特殊关卡设计背后基于笔刷固体的面制作的理论
comparing it to how meshes work will be the biggest workflow transition the old
其与起源1的网格固体的工作流程方式有了巨大区别
way was based on having to build blocks of geometry that would require six of
起源1的地图制作方法是基于构建几何块,这需要六个几何体块
them to contain a small room for the player
才能来制作一个小房间供玩家游玩
to properly optimize The Source One workflow you would have to apply the no
而想要正确优化您必须将 Nodraw(不渲染)
draw material to the 30 faces that were not a part of what the player could see
工具材质应用到 30 个面,这些面不是玩家可以看到的
with viz working differently porting Mouse from Source one can be tedious
以及由于可视化引擎(vis)的工作方式不同,源1制作一个小房间和源2相比
compared to Source 1 making a small room and Source 2 is as easy as taking a mesh
可能会很乏味和麻烦,而起源2就直接创建一个固体
and flipping the faces inwards
然后将固体的面向内翻转就行,非常的简单
if you come from a background and modeling such as blender this process
如果您来自有建模背景的软件 (例如Blender),则此过程
becomes much more intuitive the old way needs to be let go 36 faces and Source
变得更加直观,起源1的旧方法需要36个面
One for the same result was six faces in source 2.
一为相同的结果是 6 个面源 2。
first thing is to save our map and name it a originally test Maple one changing
第一件事是保存我们的地图并将其命名为原始测试枫树,将
the grid size down here to 256 and by selecting the block tool we're now ready
网格大小更改为 256,通过选择块工具,我们现在准备好
to lay down our first mesh with Source 2 you can work primarily in the 3D view
使用源 2 放置我们的第一个网格,您可以主要工作 在 3D 视图中,
dragging across the size of the mesh on the 3D grid you can change the mesh
拖动 3D 网格上的网格大小,您可以在将
shape and size after placing it into the world
其放入世界后更改网格形状和大小,
pressing F will flip the normals of the mesh so the walls are facing inwards
按 F 将翻转网格的法线,使墙壁朝内
placing down a player info Star by selecting The Entity tool will help us
放置玩家信息星 通过选择“实体”工具将帮助我们
with figuring out scale in Hammer each unit equals one inch the
计算Hammer 中的比例,每个单位等于一英寸,
player height is 72 units tall with the camera level at 64 units
玩家高度为 72 个单位,相机级别为 64 个单位,
with the mesh selected you can switch between the different manipulation
选择网格后,您可以在不同的操作
points such as vertices edges faces and the entire object by pressing shift one
点之间切换,例如顶点、边缘、面通过按 Shift 1
through five this makes it easy later to fine tune our editing
到 5 来显示整个对象,这使得以后可以轻松地微调我们的编辑,
the light environment entity will be used to provide us with a consistent
光环境实体将用于为我们提供
light source applied across the entirety of the map it doesn't matter where you
应用于整个地图的一致光源,无论您放在哪里都没关系
put this just the angle of the entity that determines where the sun is
这只是实体的角度,决定了太阳在
to switch between the window lighting modes select from the drop down menu are
窗口照明模式之间切换的位置,从下拉菜单中选择是
first of a couple of options all lighting or press F6
几个选项中的第一个,所有照明或按 F6
the more powerful and Superior option that is new to Counter-Strike 2 is a GPU
是 Counter 新增的更强大和更高级的选项 -  Strike 2 是 GPU
path tracing option or alt F6 there was no light in either of those options
路径跟踪选项或 alt F6,这两个选项中都没有光,
because new to Source 2 is Counter-Strike 2's backface block light
因为 Source 2 的新功能是Counter-Strike 2 的背面阻挡光,
which was stopping any of the light going in for now we're going to delete
它阻止了任何进入的光,现在我们要删除
the face just to show how this feature works and later replace the face with a
脸部只是为了展示此功能的工作原理,然后用
proper meshing material applied you'll notice in all lighting mode that there
应用的适当网格材质替换脸部,您会注意到在所有照明模式下,
are tiny slivers of light seeping through the seams this is normally
有微小的光线从接缝中渗出,这通常是
because all lighting uses v-rad too as a preview not accurate of the final
因为所有照明也都使用 v-rad 作为最终产品的预览不准确,
product going to the new GPU path tracing view will give you a near
进入新的 GPU 路径跟踪视图将为您提供近乎
perfect replication of what the final compile will look like this is a massive
完美的最终编译结果的复制,这也是
change to Source too and eliminates the guesswork of how baking and light Maps
对源代码的巨大更改,并消除了如何烘焙和光照贴图的猜测
will compile
将编译
press Ctrl Z to undo deleting the mesh and instead with it selected in face
按 Ctrl Z 撤消删除网格,而是在面
mode browse through the materials and search for the Skybox material selecting
模式中选择它浏览材质并搜索天空盒材质选择
this and pressing shift T will apply the material to the selected faces
此材质并按 Shift T 会将材质应用到选定的面
I'll explain why this affects viz later to hide all the cool materials and
我将解释为什么这会影响即 稍后要隐藏所有很酷的材质和
entities press shift o to hide and unhide them
实体,请按 Shift o
back in the material editor let's get some proper Dev tool materials it
在材质编辑器中隐藏和取消隐藏它们,让我们获取一些适当的开发工具材质,如果
wouldn't be a source block out without some orange and gray we can double click
没有一些橙色和灰色,我们可以双击网格,它就不会成为
on the mesh to select all the faces in it and holding Ctrl click to deselect
源块 选择其中的所有面并按住 Ctrl 单击以取消选择
the floor and Sky apply the textures with shift T and then by clicking align
地板和天空 使用Shift T 应用纹理,然后单击“对齐
to grid use each of these squares to eyeball every eight Hammer units
到网格” 使用这些方块中的每一个来观察每八个 Hammer 单元
this particular layout is going to have orange walls and gray floors
这个特定的布局将具有橙色墙壁
for our first hallway select these two edges and press V to make an edge cut we
我们的第一个走廊的灰色地板选择这两个边缘并按 V 进行边缘切割,我们
press F to Bevel The Edge and can now move each Edge individually by pressing
按 F 使边缘成斜角,现在可以在
T to go into transform mode when we have made the edges of the hallway wide
制作走廊边缘时按 T 进入变换模式来单独移动每个边缘
enough on each side we can combine the two faces next to each other by
每边足够宽,我们可以通过
selecting them and pressing backspace
选择它们并按退格键将彼此相邻的两个面组合起来。
we can add cuts to our faces by selecting the face and pressing shift X
我们可以通过选择面并按 Shift X
to go into clipping mode make sure to select to keep the faces and now drag a
进入剪切模式来添加剪切到我们的面,请确保选择保留面和 现在,在
line across the face where you want to make your cut press enter for a single
要进行剪切的面上拖一条线,
cut or space if you want to make multiple cuts
如果要进行多次剪切,请按 Enter 键进行单次剪切或空格,按住 Shift 键并选择
holding down shift with the hallway face selected and pressing T to be in
走廊面,然后按 T 进入
transform mode drag the arrow to extrude the face this method of mesh creation
变换模式,拖动箭头以挤出面这种网格创建方法
will be our bread and butter and Source 2 Hammer let's find the quad slice tool
将成为我们的面包和黄油,Source2 Hammer 让我们
under faces options to show another method to create a hallway with the
在面选项下找到四边形切片工具,以显示另一种创建走廊的方法,并选择
adjacent wall face selected adjust the number of X and Y cuts and click slice
相邻的墙面,调整X 和 Y 切割的数量,然后单击 切片
to prepare another face to extrude we want to make sure that the height of
以准备另一面进行挤出,我们要确保
these hallways are at least 128 units preferably 144 to 160 for proper scale
这些走廊的高度至少为 128 个单位,最好是 144 到 160,以实现适当的比例,
with a 2d view from top helping align the grid we're going to press insert to
并从顶部查看 2D 视图,帮助对齐我们将按插入键
go into pivot editing mode and move the pivot away from the center of the face
进入的网格 枢轴编辑模式并将枢轴移离面部中心,
pressing R to go into rotation mode and holding shift to rotate the face along
按 R 进入旋转模式,按住 Shift 键以
with the new pivot alignment we can just go ahead and with one rotation press
沿着新的枢轴对齐方式旋转面部,我们可以继续,旋转一圈后按
shift G to repeat the last action until we complete the 90 degree Arc this third
Shift G 重复最后一次 直到我们完成 90 度弧这个第三个
hallway I'll show another technique this time it's going to require a little bit
走廊我将展示另一种技术这次它需要
of prep work I'm going to make clips into the floor face and wall face at the
一点准备工作我将通过选择它们同时将夹子插入地板面和墙面
same time by selecting them and pressing shift X dragging the tool and pressing
然后按shift X拖动工具并按空格键
space to make Cuts we have now created a scaffold to use for this next part
进行剪切我们现在已经创建了一个脚手架以用于下一部分,
one tip is you can use the clipping tool to align with other cuts on the grid as
一个技巧是您可以使用剪切工具与网格上的其他剪切对齐,
well for this we're going to need to remove
为此我们将进行 需要删除
the lower face of this cut wall by selecting the face and pressing delete
此切割墙的下表面,方法是选择面并在
with the edge selected find the edge Arc tool or press y to create an arch you
选定边缘的情况下按删除找到边缘圆弧工具或按 y 创建拱形,您
can adjust it by dragging the pivot Points around and pressing enter to set
可以通过拖动枢轴点周围并按 Enter 进行设置来调整
it in stone double clicking The Edge will select the
它 在石头中双击边缘将选择
loop which was made possible by having the floor Clips we made earlier we are
循环,这是通过我们之前制作的地板夹子实现的,我们将
going to extrude using open edges and like earlier by pressing insert we can
使用开放边缘进行挤出,就像之前通过按插入一样,我们可以
adjust the pivot point of these edges lowering the angle allows us to create a
调整这些边缘的枢轴点,降低角度允许我们 为了创建
much smoother rotation than the previous hallway with these arches
比以前带有这些拱门的走廊更平滑的旋转,
so that's three separate hallways made three separate ways there is never just
因此三个独立的走廊以三种不同的方式制成,
one way to manipulate the mesh work let's give this hallway a little more
操纵网格工作的方法从来不只有一种,让我们给这个走廊更多的
variation in architecture double click on the edge to select the loop and then
建筑变化,双击边缘进行选择 循环,然后
click on bevel to bring up the toolbox where you can change the properties here
单击斜角以调出工具箱,您可以在其中更改属性,在这里我们
we go for a simple bevel to complete the hallway
使用一个简单的斜角来完成走廊,
we're going to use a scale tool for the next few parts taking the hallway and
我们将使用缩放工具来处理接下来的几个部分,选取走廊并
shift extruding the appropriate length we will push out the walls holding shift
移动挤压 适当的长度我们将推出墙壁按住shift
and scaling horizontally outwards holding alt shift and double-clicking on
并水平向外缩放按住altshift并双击
a face will select all the adjacent planar faces let's give the room a bit
一个面将选择所有相邻的平面让我们给房间多一点
more elevation to keep consistent with the other Heights of this map
的高度以与创建的地图的其他高度保持一致
creating this next room will be a bit trickier because of the beveling with
下一个房间会有点棘手,因为
these angled adjacent walls extrude out and then press e to go into scaling mode
这些有角度的相邻墙壁的斜角会挤出,然后按 e 进入缩放模式
and horizontally pull the walls in together so they now line up vertically
并将墙壁水平拉到一起,这样它们现在垂直
holding down shift and right clicking on a face will grab the face into the
排列,按住 Shift 键并右键单击一个面 将把面抓住到
active material slot this allows us to add the Skybox material to the ceiling
活动材料槽中,这使我们能够快速将天空盒材料添加到
quickly for this next room I will select the slip by double clicking the open
下一个房间的天花板上,我将通过双击打开的
Edge and deselecting the bottom Edge by holding Ctrl and clicking it press
边缘来选择滑动条,并通过按住 Ctrl 键并单击它按
insert to adjust the pivot point to the floor plane and then press e to scale
插入键来取消选择底部边缘 将枢轴点调整到地板平面,然后按 e 进行缩放
out and extrude holding shift and dragging the vertical plane outwards
并挤出,按住 Shift 并向外拖动垂直平面
now I'm going to deselect the edges that aren't part of the arc and then flatten
现在我要取消选择不属于圆弧的边缘,然后
these by pressing e and using scale on the vertical axes
按 e 和 将它们展平 使用垂直轴上的比例,
the rest of this room is made extruding out the walls and using the 2D view to
该房间的其余部分被挤出墙壁,并使用 2D 视图
make sure it is aligned ideally you want to build major mesh work on the grid
确保其理想对齐,您想要在网格上构建主要的网格工作,
with units of eight selecting two edges and pressing B will Bridge the edges
以八为单位选择两条边并按 B 将
with the new face clicking on the face and pressing alt shift and right
用新面桥接边缘,单击该面并按Alt Shift 键,然后右键
clicking on another face will apply that material and UV to the selected face
单击另一个面将将该材质和 UV 应用于所选面,
these hallways are really dark and for Counter-Strike 2 competitive play
这些走廊非常黑暗,对于《反恐精英 2》竞技游戏来说,
visibility is a major factor select every other face by holding down shift
可见性是选择的一个主要因素通过按住 Shift
and clicking them with our grid size set to 16 hold down shift and press up to
并单击它们并将网格大小设置为 16,按住 Shift 并向上按以
extrude all three faces upwards grab that Skybox material as we showed
向上挤出所有三个面,抓住天空盒材质,如我们
earlier and apply it with shift T we can immediately see how the Sky Box casts
之前所示,然后使用 Shift T 应用它,我们可以立即看到天空如何 盒子
light down from those faces for this section we can continue to make
从这些面上投射光线,在本节中,我们可以继续进行
Edge cuts which will always cut in half the face between the two edges apply the
边缘切割,这将始终将两个边缘之间的面切成两半,
Skybox material in preview with GPU path tracing
在预览中应用天空盒材质,并使用 GPU 路径跟踪,
for this final hallway the use of models will come in handy one way to access it
为最后的走廊使用模型 访问它的一种方便方法
is to open up a floating window and switch to tap to the asset browser if
是打开一个浮动窗口,然后切换到点击资产浏览器,如果
you have multiple monitors it helps to have this window on one of them
您有多个显示器,则可以在其中一个显示器上设置此窗口,
search for the word light to filter out the available models we're going to dock
搜索“light”一词以过滤掉我们正在使用的可用型号。 将此
this asset browser into the editor to keep consistent throughout the series
资源浏览器停靠到编辑器中,以在整个系列中保持一致,
dragging a model into the view we can reset its position and rotation by
将模型拖到视图中,我们可以通过
pressing Ctrl and numpad 0. this allows us to line it perfectly to the ceiling
按 Ctrl 和小键盘 0 来重置其位置和旋转。这使我们可以将其完美地排列到
add an omni light from The Entity list by clicking on the light bulb of the
天花板上,并从通过单击
model we just placed down with Counter-Strike 2 GPU path tracing we can
我们刚刚使用Counter-Strike 2 GPU 路径跟踪放置的模型的灯泡,我们可以
modify the omniolite properties directly on The View screen or through object
直接在视图屏幕上修改 Omniolite 属性,或者通过对象
properties these new Omni 2 lights as well as all the lighting entities will
属性修改这些新 Omni 2 灯以及所有照明的实体列表 实体将
have their own video that goes into much more detail for now we're just getting
有自己的视频,其中包含更多详细信息,现在我们只是记录一些内容,
down something that we can later refine in object mode with the model and light
稍后我们可以在对象模式中细化这些内容,同时选择模型和灯光
entity both selected hold down shift and drag a copy of the selection to the
实体,按住 Shift 键并将选择的副本拖动到
opposite side and middle of the hallway making sure the light spread is
相反的位置 走廊的侧面和中间,确保光线传播
consistent don't worry about how these look for now we will Mass modify them
一致,现在不要担心它们的外观,我们稍后会对它们进行大规模修改,
later let's make sure the other ceilings have
让我们确保其他天花板
the Skybox material apply to it for this missing face we can add that in by
应用了天空盒材质,对于这个缺失的面,我们可以添加 通过
selecting the loop and pressing P to fill it in
选择循环并按 P填充它,
we have to add connecting hallways between the three mid rooms and we're
我们必须在三个中间房间之间添加连接走廊,我们
going to do that by clipping across all the faces that will connect them similar
将通过剪切所有连接它们的面来实现这一点,类似于
to earlier we're going to select all the faces clip the width of the hallways and
之前我们要选择的 所有的面都剪裁了走廊的宽度,
then delete the faces between them now comes the stitching part of the process
然后删除它们之间的面现在是过程的缝合部分,
selecting edges and bridging them together with B once the floors have
选择边缘并用 B 将它们桥接在一起,一旦地板
been connected we can easily extrude the wall edges upwards and then Bridge a
连接好,我们就可以轻松地将墙边缘向上挤出,然后桥接 a 将
ceiling connecting the rest of the seams together may require cleaning up of the
其余接缝连接在一起的天花板可能需要清理
UVS and materials or the dev textures that we've been using
我们
with the entire match selected in object mode clip out the half of the connecting
在对象模式中选择的整个匹配中使用的 UVS 和材质或开发纹理,
hallways for the sake of time and keeping things symmetrical we are going
为了时间和保持,剪掉连接走廊的一半 东西对称,我们将为
to set up a mirror for the map and this is the Midway point with the mesher
地图设置一个镜子,这是选定网格器的中途点,
selected press Ctrl F and drag a line to mirror the mesh
按 Ctrl F 并拖动一条线来镜像网格,按
press enter to finish the mirror and immediately let's clip the hallway
Enter 完成镜子,然后立即让我们剪辑
length of the Terrace side down since they should have a shorter distance to
露台的走廊长度 侧面朝下,因为它们应该与炸弹侧面目标有更短的距离,
the bomb side targets with a couple of more Clips we can move the future T
并且有更多的剪辑,我们可以将未来的 T
spawn a little bit closer these open edges across the three
产卵移动得更近一些,
hallways can be merged Back Together by selecting the open loop from each side
可以通过从每个走廊中选择开环来将三个走廊上的开放边缘合并在一起。 侧面
and pressing M this isn't a necessity but will help us later down the line in
并按 M 这不是必需的,但这将有助于我们稍后在
the blockout process with consistency you can tell open edges from the hash
遮盖过程中保持一致性,您可以从散列标记中看出开放边缘
marks that they have we still have these two meshes split
,我们仍然有这两个网格
from the original cut and we'll take care of these later
从原始切割中分离出来,我们'稍后我们会处理这些,
grab all the light models and entities in the map by selecting one of each and
通过选择其中一个并按
pressing Ctrl alt o we can mirror these as well using the mirror tool and
Ctrl alt o 来抓取地图中的所有灯光模型和实体,我们也可以使用镜像工具镜像它们,
dragging the mirror plane to the midpoint
at any point if you want to know what the commands are press F1 to bring up
如果需要,可以将镜像平面拖动到任意点的中点 要知道命令是什么,请按 F1 调出
the search function type in the desired command to filter out results
搜索功能,
if you ever want to toggle The View for the 3D Grid at the top under view is
如果您想切换,请在所需命令中键入以过滤结果。在视图下顶部的 3D 网格视图中,
where you'll find this option let's make cylinders to break up the
您可以找到此选项,让我们做一下 圆柱体来分解
action I like to have the sides easily divisible by four and 36 sides is a
动作我喜欢让边很容易被四整除,36条边是一个
great number for that drag out the cylinder and use a scaling selection and
很大的数字,因为可以拖出圆柱体并使用缩放选择和
transform tools to finish the geometry copy each cylinder into the other two
变换工具来完成几何体将每个圆柱体复制到另外两个
runes by just shift dragging them if we instance them by modifying one we can
符文中 如果我们通过修改一个来实例化它们,只需按住 Shift 并拖动它们,我们就可以
modify them all select one of the cylinders and press Ctrl alt o now right
修改它们全部选择其中一个圆柱体,然后按 Ctrl alt o 现在右键
click and under objects click replace objects with instances double-clicking
单击,然后在对象下单击将对象替换
on an instance puts us in edit mode with one of the edges selected press G to
为实例双击实例使我们进入编辑模式选定的边缘中,按 G
select the rest of the Rings and then V to make a loop cut move the loop to near
选择其余的环,然后按 V进行循环切割,将环移动到
the top and then select one of the edges and press G and then shift 3 to select
顶部附近,然后选择其中一个边缘,按 G,然后按 Shift 3 选择环
all the faces of the Ring press e to scale and hold down shift to extrude
的所有面 按 e 进行缩放并按住 Shift 向外挤出
outwards
I'm going to commit the ultimate sin for Counter-Strike mapping and that's just
我将犯下《反恐精英》地图的终极罪孽,那就是
using nothing but crates for cover this is all for good reason though since
只使用板条箱作为掩护,这都是有充分理由的,因为用于
Statin boxes for full cover shows us an opportunity to use a physics tool
全掩护的他汀类药物盒子向我们展示了有机会使用物理工具
with one of these boxes selected press shift C to simulate physics pressing
并选择这些盒子之一,按shift C来模拟物理,按空格
spacebar will allow us to drop the static prop onto the map level with the
键将允许我们将静态道具放到地图级别上,
crate underneath we can also drag the boxes around and move them manually with
下面是板条箱,我们还可以拖动盒子并使用此工具手动移动它们
this tool giving a bit of variety to the angles
给角度带来一些变化
[Music] these lights in the hallways need to be
[音乐]走廊里的这些灯需要
adjusted isolate them by selecting one and pressing Ctrl alt o hide everything
调整 选择一个并按 Ctrl alt 来隔离它们 o
else by pressing Ctrl H unhide by pressing U we can also have it only hide
按 Ctrl H 隐藏其他所有内容 按U 取消隐藏 我们也可以让它只隐藏
the selected object by pressing h we're going to group these objects as
选定的 通过按 h 键,我们将在
instances after selecting one and then selecting them all then select all other
选择一个对象后将这些对象分组为实例,然后选择所有对象,然后
Omni lights with Control Alt o and holding down control deselect one of
使用 Control Alt o 选择所有其他全向灯,并按住control 取消选择其中一个对象,
them and delete the rest now with the last omni light we use Ctrl
然后使用最后一个全向灯删除其余对象 我们使用 Ctrl
X to cut the light and then double click the instance it was on and press Ctrl
X 剪切灯光,然后双击它所在的实例,然后按 Ctrl
shift V to paste special leave the default settings and click OK paste the
shift V 粘贴特殊内容,保留默认设置,然后单击“确定”,将
light exactly it was earlier in the same spot
灯光与之前的灯光完全粘贴到同一位置
Now by editing just one of these lights in an instance we can affect the value
现在只需编辑其中一个在一个实例中,我们可以影响较长走廊一侧
of all of them throughout the entire level
整个关卡中所有灯光的值,
on the longer hallway side select the CT spawn point in the entity list and place
在实体列表中选择 CT 生成点,然后
down one rotate it to face towards the middle as where the face does determine
放置一个旋转使其面向中间,因为面确实确定了
the direction in game make a few copies of the spawn ideally having about 16
方向 在游戏中制作一些生成点的副本,理想情况下有大约 16 个
spawn points spaced 128 units apart from each other and the wall
生成点,彼此间隔 128 个单位,并且墙壁
make sure that these are lifted 16 units above the ground to prevent any
确保它们被提升到地面以上 16 个单位,以防止
Collision issues on spawn we need to tell the game which spawn points are
生成时出现任何碰撞问题,我们需要告诉游戏哪个生成点 生成点
used for 5v5 competitive play so select 5 of the spawn points and change your
用于 5v5 竞争性游戏,因此选择5 个生成点并将
spawn priority to one hide them with h and then select the rest of the spawn
生成优先级更改为 1 用 h 隐藏它们,然后选择其余的生成
points and change their priority to two for non-competitive spawns
点并将其优先级更改为 2(对于非竞争性生成)
to create the buy Zone boundaries we're going to use a mesh with the trigger
以创建购买 区域边界我们将使用带有触发材料的网格,
material that will Define the volume of the Spy Zone search for the trigger
该网格将定义搜索触发材料的间谍区域的体积,
material and then create a new mesh with its boundaries slightly extended beyond
然后创建一个新的网格,其边界稍微超出
the room itself under object properties click tie
房间本身,在对象属性下单击绑定
selected mesh to entity and then change the entity type to func by Zone
选定的网格 到实体,然后将实体类型更改为 func by Zone,
a team number of three is used for the CT side
CT 侧使用三人团队,
with the buy Zone mesh selected and all the CT spawn points we're going to use a
选择购买区域网格,所有CT 生成点我们将使用
mirror tool to quickly create the Terrace spawn side adjust the mirror
镜像工具快速创建露台生成点 侧面调整镜像
plane to correctly align the entities and press enter
平面以正确对齐实体,然后在选择
with all the CT spawn points selected let's hide everything else so we can
所有 CT 生成点的情况下按 Enter 键让我们隐藏其他所有内容,这样我们可以
easily select just entity if we want to modify change this group of entities to
轻松地仅选择实体(如果我们想要修改),更改这组实体以向
info player terrorist note that all the competitive spawn
玩家恐怖分子提供信息,请注意所有竞争性 生成
point values are kept change the terrorist Funk buy Zone to a team number
点值保持不变,将恐怖分子 Funk 购买区域更改为
of two and we're all set to create bomb site a we create a new mesh with the
两人团队,我们准备好创建炸弹地点,我们使用触发材料创建一个新网格,
trigger material and tie this to an entity called Funk bomb Target the first
并将其与名为 Funk 炸弹的实体绑定起来,瞄准第一个
bomb site created will always be bomb site a and the second will be bomb site
炸弹 创建的站点将始终是炸弹站点 A,第二个将是炸弹站点
B
B,
without any idea where to go we need to toss in some overlays to direct players
不知道该去哪里,我们需要添加一些覆盖层以将玩家引导
to the bomb sites in the asset browser find the tab overlays and search for
至资源浏览器中的炸弹站点,找到选项卡覆盖层并搜索
bomb to filter out A and B targets drag and drop the overlay into the 3D View
要过滤的炸弹 出 A 和 B 目标,将覆盖层拖放到 3D 视图中,
and rotate and scale it into its desired location
然后旋转并缩放到所需位置,
with some arrows to point out the direction we're almost finished if we
用一些箭头指出我们即将完成的方向,如果我们
want to mirror and overlay we can it will also mirror the image in that
想要镜像和覆盖,我们可以它也将镜像 该
overlay as well with the overlays for the Terrace side
覆盖层中的图像以及露台一侧的覆盖层
finished we can copy and rotate them to the other side so the counter terrorists
完成后,我们可以将它们复制并旋转到另一侧,以便反恐分子
also know where to go we didn't mirror these because it would have made the
也知道要去哪里,我们没有镜像这些,因为它会使
letters backwards to highlight the bomb site area to the
字母向后突出以突出显示 玩家的炸弹地点区域,
player we're going to add overlays that match the boundaries of the trigger mesh
我们将添加与触发网格边界相匹配的覆盖层,
the next set of entities involve the team selection introduction and winter
下一组实体涉及团队选择介绍和冬季
screens this can be done in the playable space of the map or anywhere you want to
屏幕,这可以在地图的可玩空间或任何您想要的地方完成 将
place it for this video we will create a separate part of the world just for
其放置在此视频中,我们将为这些实体创建一个单独的世界部分,
these entities this separate area will carry the same
这个单独的区域将具有相同的
consistent measurements and Dev theme of orange walls and gray floors
一致尺寸和橙色墙壁和灰色地板的开发主题,
for our first entity search for counter terrorist team intro in the entity list
用于我们在实体列表中搜索反恐团队介绍的第一个实体
and place down where you want the view to be based on the camera model shown
并根据现在显示的相机模型放置在您想要视图的位置
for now just copy The Entity and rename it to quickly add more to the map rename
只需复制实体并重命名它以快速添加更多内容到地图中将其重命名
this one to terrorist team intro and find an ankle that gets their best side
为恐怖分子团队介绍并找到一个脚踝,让他们在下一个阶段获得最好的一面
the next entity is for the winning team who get to flex on the losers with
实体是为获胜团队设计的,他们可以在回合结束时对失败者进行调整,
entity end of round and the last entity for these Polaroid
而这些宝丽来时刻的最后一个实体
moments is a team select entity that requires a little bit more space
是一个团队选择实体,需要更多一点的空间,
each team should get their own ride to make their stance a little more menacing
每个团队都应该有自己的骑行来使自己的立场成为可能 更具威胁性的是,
our CTS get a nice compact car they rolled through in opposite of this
我们的 CTS 得到了一辆漂亮的紧凑型汽车,他们在这辆
Decked Out sedan that the terror is strapped into the winning team ends up
Decked Out 轿车的对面滚过,恐怖被绑在获胜的团队中,在
with this blazing station wagon for this final piece during team select we have
团队选择期间,最后一块是这辆燃烧的旅行车,我们有
the back of a lift that has been buried into the ground with some Physics Magic
电梯的后面 已经通过一些物理魔法埋入地下,
let's give these cars a fresh paint job by selecting them and an object property
让我们通过选择它们和选择颜色的对象属性来为这些汽车进行新的油漆工作,
selecting color you can use the Color Picker to try and match them but the
您可以使用颜色选择器来尝试匹配它们,但
color red seems to be in style continue to tint the remaining collection of
红色似乎继续流行为剩余的
vehicles adding color to your map and editor palette favorites as you go along
车辆集合着色 为您的地图和编辑器调色板收藏夹添加颜色 当您沿着
our Cube maps and light Pros will be placed down in an entity that combines
立方体地图和灯光 Pros 进行操作时,它们将被放置在一个实体中,该实体将
them called combined Cube map and light probe volume Place one from the NC list
它们组合在一起,称为组合立方体贴图和灯光探针体积 将 NC 列表中的一个放入
into the map and make sure that the circle entity is about 64-72 units above
地图并确保圆形实体距地面约 64-72 个单位,
the ground where the player's eye level will mostly be you can press insert to
玩家的视线高度将在该位置,如果需要,您可以按插入键
manually move this around if needed and close the boundaries of the volume into
手动移动它,并将体积的边界关闭到
the room itself this tells the engine where to calculate the light maps and
房间本身中,这告诉您 引擎在哪里计算光照贴图以及在
where to project the cube map to you should try to have one of these
哪里投影立方体贴图您应该尝试让每个房间或走廊
combined light probe Cube map volumes in each room or hallway centered as much as
中的这些组合光探针立方体贴图体积之一
possible it is okay to overlap them slightly and better to overlap than
尽可能居中,可以稍微重叠它们,最好 重叠比
underlap Counter-Strike 2 now Blends the cube Maps along the edges to make the
下重叠 现在《反恐精英 2》沿着边缘混合立方体贴图,使
transition appear seamless this is one of the most tedious tasks doing this
过渡显得无缝 这是最繁琐的任务之一 正确执行此操作,
correctly since each room and hallway will be unique in its setup the easiest
因为每个房间和走廊的设置都是独一无二的 最简单
but worth quality solution would be to place one giant Cube map for the whole
但值得的优质解决方案为整个地图放置一个巨大的立方体贴图,
map which can work well for testing until the end when you will want to make
这可以很好地进行测试,直到最后,当您想要
sure to go back and optimize them if we merge the mesh splits in the
确保返回并优化它们时,如果我们合并
ceiling of these three mid rooms we can expand the Sky Box upwards to be able to
这三个中间房间天花板上的网格分割,我们可以扩展 天空盒向上,以便能够在
fit a combined light probe Cube map above the central cylinder this is one
中心圆柱体上方安装组合光探头立方体贴图,这是
approach to having this architecture where the light probe would otherwise be
实现这种架构的一种方法,否则光探头将
trapped inside a mesh the alternative approach would be to split up the room
被困在网格内,另一种方法是将房间分成
into quadrants and place a combined light probe Cube map in the middle of
象限 并在每个立方体贴图的中间放置一个组合的光探针立方体贴图,
each the reason why we merge the open edges is to make sure the Extrusion up
我们合并开放边缘的原因是为了确保向上挤压
doesn't contain the split end face Extrusion that would go with it
不包含分裂端面挤压,
if you know the layout and measurements will allow for it you can always copy
如果您知道布局和测量将随之而来 考虑到这一点,您可以随时
over combine light Pro queue maps and then adjust to each Dimension to speed
复制组合光 Pro 队列图,然后调整到每个维度以
up the process
加快该过程,
once you have finished covering the map in these combined light probe Cube Maps
一旦您完成这些组合光探针立方体贴图中的覆盖范围,请
check the coverage to make sure you didn't miss a spot by selecting them all
检查覆盖范围以确保您没有错过任何一个 通过选择它们全部来
to place down a 2d Sky select Skybox from The Entity list and place it down
放置 2d 天空,从实体列表中选择天空盒并将其放置在
the default Skybox for now will do which will be shown in the all lighting
默认的天空盒中,现在将执行此操作,这将在所有照明
preview mode it does not appear on the GPU path tracing preview however but
预览模式中显示,但它不会出现在GPU 路径跟踪预览中,但是
will be there on full compile for our Counter-Strike 2 map info we
将在我们的《反恐精英 2》地图信息的完整编译中出现,我们
need to set down an infomap parameters entity no need for additional
需要设置一个信息地图参数实体,不需要额外的
configuration required and this post-processing volume I could only grab
配置,并且我只能
from the default Counter-Strike example map that was used to reference the
从使用的默认《反恐精英》示例地图中获取此后处理量 要引用
requirements I couldn't get it from The Entity list scroll down or by manually
要求,我无法从实体列表中向下滚动或手动
typing it in so for now grab it from the default map
输入它来获取它,因此现在从默认地图
place down a cube map fog entity even if we end up not really using it to blend
位置向下抓取立方体贴图雾实体,即使我们最终没有真正使用它来混合
the distance in for this test map for our basic environment sound entity
在此测试地图中,我们的基本环境声音实体的距离
select the soundscape entity and place them around the map for now each of the
选择音景实体并将它们放置在地图周围,现在
three pillars will have its own Ambience and adjusting the radius of the
三个支柱中的每一个都将有自己的氛围,调整
soundscape allows us to visualize where players will hear the sound from there
音景的半径使我们能够可视化玩家将在哪里听到声音 来自那里的声音
is a variety of sound events you can open and reference and even listen to in
有多种声音事件,您可以打开和参考,甚至在导航网格的编辑器中收听
the editor for the nav mesh you can use entity
您可以使用可
Point nav lockable and place it on the floor surface
锁定的实体点导航并将其放置在地板表面上,
click on the navigation editor button and then preview nav to have the engine
单击导航编辑器按钮,然后预览导航 让引擎向
show you where AI will be able to move around notice that there is no Blue
您显示人工智能能够在哪里移动请注意,用于团队介绍的地图的
Navigation shown in the separate part of the map used for team intros
单独部分中没有显示蓝色导航 大纲
the outliner is a powerful tool with an even more powerful inspector report that
是一个强大的工具,具有更强大的检查员报告,
we will go over in another video for now if you type in the name of what you are
我们将对此进行介绍 现在在另一个视频中,如果您输入要查找的内容的名称,它将
looking for it will appear in the outliner filter select it and press Ctrl
出现在大纲过滤器中,选择它并按 Ctrl、
shift e to Center the camera on what you are looking for this can be used to
shift e 将相机置于您要查找的内容的中心,这可用于
search for anything that is in the map and is built on the history of what and
搜索任何 位于地图中,并建立在历史记录之上,
when you have placed it down let's add the light map player space
当您将其放下时,让我们添加光照贴图玩家空间
mesh which requires us to find the material tools light map res and create
网格,这需要我们找到材质工具光照贴图资源并在
a volume around all the parts of the map that the player is able to stand on with
地图的所有部分周围创建一个体积玩家能够站在离
its height 128 units above the floor this will tell the engine where to
地面 128 个单位的高度上,这将告诉引擎在哪里
increase light map bias the further away from this volume the less bias it will
增加光照贴图偏差,距离该体积越远,偏差就越小,
have you can cover the map for this test map but for more intricate Maps you will
您可以覆盖此测试地图的地图,但更多 复杂的地图,您将
need more attention to detail with so many brushes as entities
需要更多地关注细节,因为实体开始构建如此多的画笔,
beginning to build up it might start to get in our way of our work we can use
它可能会开始妨碍我们的工作,我们可以使用
the out of this selector to tick on or off parts of the map that you want to
此选择器的外面来勾选或关闭您想要的地图部分 要
see in the editor keep in mind that this is just the in editor view these will
在编辑器中查看,请记住,这只是编辑器视图中的视图,这些视图
still compile
仍将编译
to verify what is contributing to Vis click on the viz contributors button to
以验证对 Vis 有贡献的内容,单击可视化贡献者按钮以
see what is going to be calculated so far we have gone through the level of
查看将计算的内容,到目前为止,我们已经完成了以下级别
field that with good viz practices this means that we don't have any holes that
通过良好的可视化实践,这意味着我们没有任何
would affect it you'll also notice that props whether static or dynamic are
会影响它的漏洞,您还会注意到,无论是静态还是动态的道具都被
removed we're going to have to separate video that goes into depth about Fizz
删除了,我们将不得不分离深入了解 Fizz 的视频,
but to summarize this is what tells the engine what to draw and when to draw
但为了 总结一下,这就是告诉引擎要绘制什么以及何时绘制
Source 2 viz Works a little different than Source One did and to see how good
源 2 viz 的工作方式与源 1 稍有不同,为了了解好
viz versus bad Vis looks like we'll show you in this demonstration here we're
可视化与坏可视化的外观,我们将在此处的演示中向您展示,我们
going to remove the entire face of the ceiling in the intro group and then
将 删除介绍组中天花板的整个面,然后
compile the map using full compile this will build a DOT Los file which will be
使用完整编译来编译地图,这将构建一个 DOT Los 文件,该文件将
based on the viz that was compiled we can then load this into the editor after
基于编译的可视化项,然后我们可以在地图编译后将其加载到编辑器中
a map has compiled to check Vis go to map and load compiled Vis data this will
检查 Vis 转到地图并加载已编译的 Vis 数据,这将向
show you how the map is chunked into sections you'll notice how these chunks
您展示地图如何分成多个部分,您会注意到这些块如何
conform to the interior of the player space except for the one part where we
符合玩家空间的内部,除了我们
deleted the mesh entirely this viz leak was the engine attempting to see into
完全删除网格的部分(此可视化泄漏)引擎试图查看
the void select the loop and press P to on the face and with the correct Skybox
虚空,选择循环并在面上按 P,并应用正确的 Skybox
material applied we can see in the sequential compile and reloading of viz
材质,我们可以在可视化数据的顺序编译和重新加载中看到
data how this is fixed our Vis leak from earlier badvis will result in bad
这是如何修复的,我们从早期 badvis 中产生的 Vis 泄漏将导致 在
performance and things popping in and out
性能不佳和突然出现的情况下,
let's go with the different compile options starting with fast compile this
让我们使用不同的编译选项,从快速编译开始,这
takes seconds and it's useful if you're just testing out the geometry and
需要几秒钟的时间,如果您只是测试
physics of a build and don't care for lighting everything here is using vrad 2
构建的几何和物理并且不关心这里的所有内容,那么它很有用 使用 vrad 2,
which is vertex lighting and not representative of the final product at
它是顶点照明,根本不代表最终产品,
all
clicking on full compile will build the level with the 1K standard light map the
单击完整编译将使用 1K 标准光照贴图构建关卡,
default settings will also have this compile viz giving you a good look at
默认设置也将具有此编译可视化,让您可以很好地查看
the final product you'll notice how true the GPU path tracing preview is to the
最终产品 您会注意到GPU 路径跟踪预览对于
compile the higher the light map resolution the
编译的真实性光照贴图分辨率越高,
sharper the shadows and the more luxles used the highest possible production
阴影越锐利,使用的勒克斯越多 最高可能的作品
will be 8K with a quality of final be warned that you will need a large amount
将是 8K,最终质量警告您将需要大量
of system Ram if you don't want the compiler to fail for CPU related tasks
的 系统 RAM 如果您不希望编译器在执行与 CPU 相关的任务(
such as Vis the higher the core threads count the better you have to have a ray
例如 Vis)时失败,则核心线程数越高,您必须拥有光线
tracing video card or this compiler won't work
追踪显卡,否则该编译器将无法工作,
what this compiler is making is a VPK file that is a ZIP file containing all
该编译器正在制作的是 VPK文件是一个 ZIP 文件,包含
the info for the map in your game folder once the compiler is finished enjoy the
游戏文件夹中地图的所有信息,编译完成后,享受
world that you have created and step into a shootout with some Bots grenades
您创建的世界,并使用一些机器人手榴弹进入枪战,这些手榴弹
will go through the sky box and remain in the level of play if you have set up
将穿过天空盒并保留在关卡中 如果你正确设置了
the navigation mesh entity correctly Bots will be able to move around the
导航网格实体,机器人将能够在
objective points work together plant the bomb and defend it the next steps after
目标点周围移动,一起放置炸弹并防御它,接下来的步骤
this would be to refine the gameplay before beginning an art path
是在开始艺术路径之前完善游戏玩法
and that's it for our first Counter-Strike 2 mapping Academy
,仅此而已 我们的第一个《反恐精英 2》地图学院
tutorial I'm Sammy chimoni hihiala yubi I hope you enjoyed this video like
教程 我是 Sammy chimoni hihiala yubi我希望您喜欢这个视频,喜欢
comment subscribe and support us by following the link to our Discord
评论订阅并通过我们的 Discord 链接支持我们